Junior Software Developer III ROBERT SMITH

Phone: (123) 456 78 99 Email: info@qwikresume.com Website: www.qwikresume.com

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/qwikresume Address: 1737 Marshville Road,

labama.

Objective

Junior Software Developer III with 8 years of experience in the IT domain is seeking to pursue an opportunity with a growing organization that will utilize and enhance my knowledge in software development, and that will provide me with essential growth opportunities.

Skills

Router Configuration, Port Forwarding, Firewall, Content Deployment, GIMP, CRON, SMTP, POP3, Windows, Linux, CentOS, Red Hat, Mint Fedora, Ubuntu, Mac OSX, PHP, HTML, CSS, Pawn, Bash, SQL, Javascript, C#, Objective-C, Unity Script, MySQL, MariaDB, PostgreSQL, Geany, PhpStorm, Stash, Jira, GIT

Work Experience

Junior Software Developer III

Sicom Systems - April 2010 - Present

- Participating in daily scrum meetings, sprint planning, unit testing and bug fixes.
- Developing and maintaining a reporting system for support users, managers and executives to keep track of support calls both on a moment to moment basis and over time using PHP, MySQL, HTML, and CSS.
- Assisting the Senior Developer with the design, development, deployment, and maintenance of all menu maintenance portal code using PHP, MySQL, HTML, CSS, and Javascript.
- The menu maintenance portal is a web-based system that allows users to manage all of the settings for each of their restaurants in one place.
- In charge of all content deployment for digital menu boards and management training systems.
- Working closely with the QA and Product Management teams as well as other developers to ensure quality and punctual software development.
- Troubleshooting server communication and any potential Cron, SMTP or POP3 issues.

Junior Software Developer III

ABC Corp - 2009 - 2010

- Met or exceeded the daily call goals and striving to achieve excellent customer satisfaction.
- Trained new employees. Created and maintained good relationships with customers.
- Generated an internal data analysis assistance program utilizing PHP and MySQL, optimizing classification of the stock market.
- Created and managed frontend and backend of a stock market analysis website for individual investment decision-making.
- Developed WCF class library to utilize web service maintained by teammates.
- Investigated and introduced Xamarin to create a cross-platform mobile application of the management system.
- This is Dummy Description data, Replace with job description relevant to your current role. In case if you dont need it you can delete it.

Education
Education Bachelors in Computer Science - 2013 to 2018(Bucks County Community College - Newtown, PA)